<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
    <rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
        <channel>
        <atom:link href="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/litlitlitlit.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
            <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT</title>
            <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT is a bi-monthly literary event in Vancouver, BC that simply invites FOUR writers, poets and/or artists at a time to read their work to interested parties. LIT LIT LIT LIT is organized by Steffanie Ling and Emma Metcalfe Hurst.</description>
            <link>http://lit-lit-lit-lit.tumblr.com</link>
            <language>en-ca</language>
            <copyright>Creative Commons</copyright>
            <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 11:50:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 11:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
            <webMaster>elizibin@gmail.com</webMaster>
            <itunes:author>Produced by Emma Metcalfe Hurst and Steffanie Ling</itunes:author>
            <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT is a bi-monthly literary event in Vancouver, BC that simply invites FOUR writers, poets and/or artists at a time to read their work to interested parties.</itunes:subtitle>
            <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT is a bi-monthly literary event in Vancouver, BC that simply invites FOUR writers, poets and/or artists at a time to read their work to interested parties. LIT LIT LIT LIT is organized by Steffanie Ling and Emma Metcalfe Hurst.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:owner>
                <itunes:name>Emma M H</itunes:name>
                <itunes:email>emmametcalfehurst@gmail.com</itunes:email>
            </itunes:owner>
            <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:image href="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/img/dulcelitbig.jpg" />
            <itunes:category text="Arts">
                <itunes:category text="Literature" />
            </itunes:category>
            <!-- Begin Items -->
            <item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
              <!-- LIT I PART I -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->  

                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part I: Zebulon Zang and Kara Hansen</title>
                <link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT1P1.mp3</link>
                <guid>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT1P1.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Avenue 165 East Hastings St. Vancouver BC - Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen, Alex Bovril, and Steffanie Ling. April 18th 2015 8:00pm. Asked to write a biography to accompany a reading, the writer can’t think of anything to write about himself. Does he give the names of cities, institutions, achievements? What achievements? He steps out for fresh air. During, a car (on which the painter’s ladders are piled) drives up. The writer asks the painter for help with the biography and the painter agrees, but they end up talking only about window cleaning. The painter wishes he could write: when you do condos you’re cleaning these windows that take, like, half a minute, and all day long briefly glimpsing hundreds of bedrooms, which is to say of hundreds of unconnected lives—or lives that just seemed unconnected but which in writing could take on connections—the painter gets to thinking. They finish enjoying the fresh air and part ways, the writer still not knowing what to say about himself. For now, Alex Bovril is a writer currently based in New York. Kara Hansen is an artist and writer living in Nanaimo and based in Vancouver. Currently she holds the position of Curatorial Intern at the Nanaimo Art Gallery. She and Jesse Birch are co-curating an exhibition entitled Spirit Gum at the Nanaimo Art Gallery come May. From time to time she bribes the karaoke guy with flowers for two songs instead of one. Steffanie Ling is a writer, curator and editor. She will have red wine and turtlenecks all year long. For LIT LIT LIT LIT she will be reading from work in process, tentatively titled “You’re a liar and a smoker” a book of twenty chapters for twenty cigarettes. Zebulon Zang is a filmmaker and writer from Maillardville, British Columbia. He is also the founder of the Maillardville Cultural Appreciation Society, an exhibition space dedicated to the promotion of culture in peripheral zones.</description>
                <enclosure url="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT1P1.mp3" length="34192606" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:44:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part 1: New readings written and given by Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen. </itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part 1: Zebulon Zang and Kara Hansen: 
LIT LIT LIT LIT I took place at Avenue  in Vancouver BC on April 18th, 2015. New readings were written and given by 
Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen, Alex Bovril and Steffanie Ling. 

Kara Hansen’s reading “I’d Hurt A Fly, I Don’t Care If I Kill A Fly, I’d Kill A Fly“ and 
Steffanie Ling’s reading “Clean Indoor Air Act (Act 1 and 2 of 3)“ are available as limited edition chap books, published and distributed by the Somewhat Urgent Series Press. </itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:49:32</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
            <!-- LIT I PART II  -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

             <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part II: Alex Bovril and Steffanie Ling</title>
                <link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT1P2.mp3</link>
                <guid>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT1P2.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Avenue 165 East Hastings St. Vancouver BC - Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen, Alex Bovril, and Steffanie Ling. April 18th 2015 8:00pm. Asked to write a biography to accompany a reading, the writer can’t think of anything to write about himself. Does he give the names of cities, institutions, achievements? What achievements? He steps out for fresh air. During, a car (on which the painter’s ladders are piled) drives up. The writer asks the painter for help with the biography and the painter agrees, but they end up talking only about window cleaning. The painter wishes he could write: when you do condos you’re cleaning these windows that take, like, half a minute, and all day long briefly glimpsing hundreds of bedrooms, which is to say of hundreds of unconnected lives—or lives that just seemed unconnected but which in writing could take on connections—the painter gets to thinking. They finish enjoying the fresh air and part ways, the writer still not knowing what to say about himself. For now, Alex Bovril is a writer currently based in New York. Kara Hansen is an artist and writer living in Nanaimo and based in Vancouver. Currently she holds the position of Curatorial Intern at the Nanaimo Art Gallery. She and Jesse Birch are co-curating an exhibition entitled Spirit Gum at the Nanaimo Art Gallery come May. From time to time she bribes the karaoke guy with flowers for two songs instead of one. Steffanie Ling is a writer, curator and editor. She will have red wine and turtlenecks all year long. For LIT LIT LIT LIT she will be reading from work in process, tentatively titled “You’re a liar and a smoker” a book of twenty chapters for twenty cigarettes. Zebulon Zang is a filmmaker and writer from Maillardville, British Columbia. He is also the founder of the Maillardville Cultural Appreciation Society, an exhibition space dedicated to the promotion of culture in peripheral zones.</description>
                <enclosure url="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT1P2.mp3" length="42032885" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part 2: New readings written and given by Alex Bovril and Steffanie Ling </itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part 2: Alex Bovril and Steffanie Ling: 
LIT LIT LIT LIT I took place at Avenue in Vancouver BC on April 18th, 2015. New readings were written and given by Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen, Alex Bovril and Steffanie Ling. Kara Hansen’s reading “I’d Hurt A Fly, I Don’t Care If I Kill A Fly, I’d Kill A Fly“ and Steffanie Ling’s reading “Clean Indoor Air Act (Act 1 and 2 of 3)“ are available as limited edition chap books, published and distributed by the Somewhat Urgent Series Press. </itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>01:36:00</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- LIT KIOSK I -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK - Alex Bovril, Ingrid Olauson and Steffanie Ling</title>
                <link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITKIOSK.mp3</link>
                <guid>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITKIOSK.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK took place at Avenue in Vancouver BC on April 19, 2015 as a part of KIOSK, a reading room installation 
curated by ddoogg. New readings were written and given by Alex Bovril, Ingrid Olauson and Steffanie Ling. </description>
                <enclosure url="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITKIOSK.mp3" length="28298621" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK - New readings written and given by Alex Bovril, Ingrid Olauson and Steffanie Ling.</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK - Alex Bovril, Ingrid Olauson and Steffanie Ling
LIT LIT LIT LIT KIOSK took place at Avenue in Vancouver BC on April 19, 2015 as a part of KIOSK, a reading room installation curated by ddoogg. New readings were written and given by Alex Bovril, Ingrid Olauson and Steffanie Ling.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:39:32</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
            <!-- LIT II PART I -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT II - Part I: Ronan Nanning-Watson and Zuzia Juszkiewicz</title>
                <link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT2P1.mp3</link>
                <guid>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT2P1.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Publication Studio: 222 E Georgia St. Vancouver BC - Bradley Iles is reading from Derby: A Poem in Six Parts, a recent collaboration with Katrina Niebergal. Reincarnation, celebrity, the nature of the self, the selfhood of nature, Mustang-transcendentalism, a poem about a movie. Bradley lives on Melville street in Vancouver. Zuzia Juszkiewicz is a fragment in some kind of multi-faceted hybrid zone or something. She was born in Gdansk, and raised in South Africa, New Zealand, and Canada. She holds a BA in Visual Arts (Vancouver), Human Geography (Vancouver) and Urbanism at AHK (Amsterdam). She collaborates with writers, musicians, filmmakers and dancers. She often works under the name Modern Catalyst, with a focus on designing cross-disciplined artists.http://modercatalyst.ca . Ronan K. Nanning-Watson is a filmmaker, writer and artist from British Columbia. His work ranges in scope, medium, and aesthetic, but is consistently uncompromising. Recently he finished his first feature film “Crusade” about a group of young hipsters who start a holy war. The next two parts in the trilogy are in preproduction. Ingrid Olauson is a writer and trawler of people’s lives. She recently wrote, produced and acted in the play and collaborative art piece Fort Eff, which debuted at Deep Blue this past May. </description>
                <enclosure url="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT2P1.mp3" length="30528110" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT II - Part I: New readings written and given by Ronan Nanning-Watson, Zuzia Juszkiewicz.</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT II - Part 1: Ronan Nanning-Watson and Zuzia Juszkiewickz
LIT LIT LIT LIT II took place at Publication Studio in Vancouver BC on June 28, 2015. New readings were written and given by Ronan Nanning-Watson, Zuzia Juszkiewicz, Bradley Iles and Ingrid Olauson.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:43:02</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
            <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT II PART II -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT II - Part II: Bradley Iles and Ingrid Olauson</title>
                <link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT2P2.mp3</link>
                <guid>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT2P2.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Publication Studio: 222 E Georgia St. Vancouver BC - Bradley Iles is reading from Derby: A Poem in Six Parts,a recent collaboration with Katrina Niebergal. Reincarnation, celebrity, the nature of the self, the selfhood of nature, Mustang-transcendentalism, a poem about a movie. Bradley lives on Melville street in Vancouver. Zuzia Juszkiewicz is a fragment in some kind of multi-faceted hybrid zone or something. She was born in Gdansk, and raised in South Africa, New Zealand, and Canada. She holds a BA in Visual Arts (Vancouver), Human Geography (Vancouver) and Urbanism at AHK (Amsterdam). She collaborates with writers, musicians, filmmakers and dancers. She often works under the name Modern Catalyst, with a focus on designing cross-disciplined artists.http://modercatalyst.ca . Ronan K. Nanning-Watson is a filmmaker, writer and artist from British Columbia. His work ranges in scope, medium, and aesthetic, but is consistently uncompromising. Recently he finished his first feature film “Crusade” about a group of young hipsters who start a holy war. The next two parts in the trilogy are in preproduction. Ingrid Olauson is a writer and trawler of people’s lives. She recently wrote, produced and acted in the play and collaborative art piece Fort Eff, which debuted at Deep Blue this past May. </description>
                <enclosure url="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT2P2.mp3" length="30381379" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:48:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT II - Part 2: New readings written and given by Bradley Iles and Ingrid Olauson.</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT II - Part 2: Bradley Iles and Ingrid Olauson 
LIT LIT LIT LIT II took place at Publication Studio in Vancouver BC on June 28, 2015. New readings written and given by Ronan Nanning-Watson, Zuzia Juszkiewicz, Bradley Iles and Ingrid Olauson.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:42:45</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
            <!-- LIT III PART I -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

               <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT III - Part I: Maia Nichols and Alex Bovril </title>
                <link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT3P1.mp3</link>
                <guid>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT3P1.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Publication Studio: 222 E Georgia St. Vancouver BC - ALEX BOVRIL is a writer and visual artist. Recently, he has been pouring colours of concrete and writing fiction. He is currently an MFA Candidate in Creative Writing at New York University.

DONATO MANCINI makes visual and procedural poetry, bookworks, and visual art. His books and chapbooks include: Snowline (2015), Buffet World (2011) Fact ‘N’ Value (2011), Hell Passport no.22 (2008), Æthel (2007), 58 Free Coffees (2006) and Ligatures (2005). Mancini’s published critical writing includes work on the archive, time and memory in Anamnesia: Unforgetting (2011), and a discourse analysis of poetry reviews in You Must Work Harder to Write Poetry of Excellence (2012). His most recent full length book, Loitersack (2014), is a labyrinthine commonplace book where critical, theoretical and para-literary tendencies intersect in the forms of poetry, poetics, theory, theory theatre, laugh particles and many many questions.

KATE MOSS is an Australian artist who works with drawing, writing, painting, sculpture, sound and performance. Her works explore the possibilities of conversation through the vernacular of landscape, rhythm and material experimentation.

MAIA NICHOLS (b. Berkeley, California) is an artist and writer. She holds a BA in Psychology and a BFA from the University of British Columbia. She is a Masters Candidate in the Department of Critical Studies at California Institute of the Arts. Her work is currently on view at Fundación Botín’s Villa Iris in Spain</description>
                <enclosure url="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT3P1.mp3" length="40507533" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:49:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT III - Part 1: New readings written and given by Maia Nichols, Alex Bovril. </itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT III - Part 1: Maia Nichols and Alex Bovril 
LIT LIT LIT LIT III took place at Publication Studio in Vancouver BC on August 2, 2015. New readings were written and given by Ronan Nanning-Watson, Zuzia Juszkiewicz, Bradley 
Iles and Ingrid Olauson. Kate Moss’ reading “Swedish Light and Other Poems“ is available as a limited edition chap book, published and distributed by the Somewhat Urgent Series Press. Alex Bovril’s reading comes from his new book “Fragments of Bismuth” a series of short stories  published and distributed by The Somewhat Urgent Series Press. </itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:56:40</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
        <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT III PART II -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT III - Part II: Kate Moss and Donato Mancini </title>
                <link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT3P2.mp3</link>
                <guid>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT3P2.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Publication Studio: 222 E Georgia St. Vancouver BC - ALEX BOVRIL is a writer and visual artist. Recently, he has been pouring colours of concrete and writing fiction. He is currently an MFA Candidate in Creative Writing at New York University.

DONATO MANCINI makes visual and procedural poetry, bookworks, and visual art. His books and chapbooks include: Snowline (2015), Buffet World (2011) Fact ‘N’ Value (2011), Hell Passport no.22 (2008), Æthel (2007), 58 Free Coffees (2006) and Ligatures (2005). Mancini’s published critical writing includes work on the archive, time and memory in Anamnesia: Unforgetting (2011), and a discourse analysis of poetry reviews in You Must Work Harder to Write Poetry of Excellence (2012). His most recent full length book, Loitersack (2014), is a labyrinthine commonplace book where critical, theoretical and para-literary tendencies intersect in the forms of poetry, poetics, theory, theory theatre, laugh particles and many many questions.

KATE MOSS is an Australian artist who works with drawing, writing, painting, sculpture, sound and performance. Her works explore the possibilities of conversation through the vernacular of landscape, rhythm and material experimentation.

MAIA NICHOLS (b. Berkeley, California) is an artist and writer. She holds a BA in Psychology and a BFA from the University of British Columbia. She is a Masters Candidate in the Department of Critical Studies at California Institute of the Arts. Her work is currently on view at Fundación Botín’s Villa Iris in Spain. </description>
                <enclosure url="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LIT3P2.mp3" length="23442418" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Thu, 5 Nov 2015 11:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT III - Part 2: New readings written and given by Kate Moss and Donato Mancini.</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT III - Part 2: Kate Moss and Donato Mancini 
LIT LIT LIT LIT III took place at Publication Studio in Vancouver BC on August 2, 2015. New readings were written and given by Maia Nichols, Alex Bovril, Kate Moss and Donato Mancini. Kate Moss’ reading “Swedish Light and Other Poems" is available as a limited edition chap book, published and distributed by the Somewhat Urgent Series Press. Alex Bovril’s reading is from his new book “Fragments of Bismuth” a series of short stories  published and distributed by The Somewhat Urgent Series Press. </itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:33:48</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
        <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT VANCOUVER ART BOOK FAIR PART I -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair - Part I: Tom Whalen and Emma Metcalfe Hurst  </title>
                <link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITVABF1.mp3</link>
                <guid>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITVABF1.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Gallery, 750 Hornby St. Vancouver BC - Tom Whalen and Emma Metcalfe Hurst.
                 </description>
                <enclosure url="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITVABF1.mp3" length="19850134" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Tue, 8 Dec 2015 11:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair - Part I: New readings written and given by Tom Whalen and Emma Metcalfe Hurst.</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair - Part I: Tom Whalen and Emma Metcalfe Hurst.
LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair took place at the Vancouver Art Gallery Vancouver BC on October 18th, 2015 as a part of KIOSK: Reading Room. New readings were written and given by Tom Whalen, Emma Metcalfe Hurst, Hugo Noriega and Zuzia Juszkiewicz. Zuzia Juszkiewicz is reading from her new book "PROGRAM", a fifty-six page poem written in 2014 published and distributed by The Somewhat Urgent Series Press.</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:20:41</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>


<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
        <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT VANCOUVER ART BOOK FAIR PART II -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair - Part II: Hugo Noriega and Zuzia Juszkiewicz</title>
                <link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITVABF2.mp3</link>
                <guid>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITVABF2.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Gallery, 750 Hornby St. Vancouver BC - Hugo Noriega and Zuzia Juszkiewicz.
                 </description>
                <enclosure url="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITVABF2.mp3" length="21876818" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Tue, 8 Dec 2015 11:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair - Part II: New readings written and given by Hugo Noriega and Zuzia Juszkiewicz.</itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair - Part II: Hugo Noriega and Zuzia Juszkiewicz.
LIT LIT LIT LIT Vancouver Art Book Fair took place at the Vancouver Art Gallery Vancouver BC on October 18th, 2015 as a part of KIOSK: Reading Room. New readings were written and given by Tom Whalen, Emma Metcalfe Hurst, Hugo Noriega and Zuzia Juszkiewicz. Zuzia Juszkiewicz is reading from her new book "PROGRAM", a fifty-six page poem written in 2014 published and distributed by The Somewhat Urgent Series Press. </itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:22:47</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
        <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT IV PART I -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV - Part I: Jacquelyn Ross and Bradley Iles </title>
                <link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITIVI.mp3</link>
                <guid>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITIVI.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV took place at 221A in Vancouver, BC on December 6, 2015. New readings were given by Jacquelyn Ross, Bradley Iles, Eli Zibin and Steffanie Ling. </description>
                <enclosure url="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITIVI.mp3" length="36529255" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 11:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV - Part I: Jacquelyn Ross and Bradley Iles </itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LLIT LIT LIT LIT IV took place at 221A in Vancouver, BC on December 6, 2015. New readings were given by Jacquelyn Ross, Bradley Iles, Eli Zibin and Steffanie Ling. 
</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:38:03</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
        <!-- LIT LIT LIT LIT IV PART II -->
<!-- *******************************************************-->
<!-- *******************************************************-->

            <item>
                <title>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV - Part II: Eli ZIbin and Steffanie Ling </title>
                <link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITIVII.mp3</link>
                <guid>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITIVII.mp3</guid>
                <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV took place at 221A in Vancouver, BC on December 6, 2015. New readings were given by Jacquelyn Ross, Bradley Iles, Eli Zibin and Steffanie Ling. </description>
                <enclosure url="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITIVII.mp3" length="39173450" type="audio/mpeg" />
                <category>Podcasts</category>
                <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2015 11:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
                <itunes:author>LIT LIT LIT LIT</itunes:author>
                <itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
                <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV - Part II: Eli ZIbin and Steffanie Ling </itunes:subtitle>
                <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT IV took place at 221A in Vancouver, BC on December 6, 2015. New readings were given by Jacquelyn Ross, Bradley Iles, Eli Zibin and Steffanie Ling. 
</itunes:summary>
                <itunes:duration>00:40:48</itunes:duration>
                <itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
            </item>

        </channel>
    </rss>