<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"  version="2.0">

  <channel>

    <title>Lit Lit Lit Lit</title>
    <description>LIT LIT LIT LIT is a bi-monthly literary event in Vancouver,BC that simply invites FOUR writers, poets and/or artists at a time to read their work to interested parties. LIT LIT LIT LIT is organized by Steffanie Ling and Emma Metcalfe Hurst.</description>
    <link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz</link>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <copyright>Creative Commons</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 11:30:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 11:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
  
    <webMaster>elizibin@gmail.com</webMaster>

    <itunes:author>emmametcalfehurst@gmail.com</itunes:author>
    <itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT is a bi-monthly literary event in Vancouver,BC that simply invites FOUR writers, poets and/or artists at a time to read their work to interested parties.</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>LIT LIT LIT LIT is a bi-monthly literary event in Vancouver,BC that simply invites FOUR writers, poets and/or artists at a time to read their work to interested parties. LIT LIT LIT LIT is organized by Steffanie Ling and Emma Metcalfe Hurst.</itunes:summary>

    <itunes:owner>
           <itunes:name>Emma M H</itunes:name>
           <itunes:email>emmametcalfehurst@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>

<itunes:image href="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/img/dulcelitbig.jpg"/>
    
<itunes:category text="Arts">
     <itunes:category text="Literature"/>
</itunes:category>


<!-- Begin Items -->

<item>
<title>LIT LIT LIT LIT I - Part I: Zebulon Zan and Kara Hansen</title>
<link>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITIPartI-ZebKara.mp3</link>
<guid>http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITIPartI-ZebKara.mp3</guid>
<description>LIT LIT LIT LIT Avenue 165 East Hastings St. Vancouver BC - Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen, Alex Bovril, and Steffanie Ling. April 18th 2015 8:00pm.
Asked to write a biography to accompany a reading, the writer can’t think of anything to write about himself. Does he give the names of cities, institutions, achievements? What achievements? He steps out for fresh air. During, a car (on which the painter’s ladders are piled) drives up. The writer asks the painter for help with the biography and the painter agrees, but they end up talking only about window cleaning. The painter wishes he could write: when you do condos you’re cleaning these windows that take, like, half a minute, and all day long briefly glimpsing hundreds of bedrooms, which is to say of hundreds of unconnected lives—or lives that just seemed unconnected but which in writing could take on connections—the painter gets to thinking. They finish enjoying the fresh air and part ways, the writer still not knowing what to say about himself. For now, Alex Bovril is a writer currently based in New York. 

Kara Hansen is an artist and writer living in Nanaimo and based in Vancouver. Currently she holds the position of Curatorial Intern at the Nanaimo Art Gallery. She and Jesse Birch are co-curating an exhibition entitled Spirit Gum at the Nanaimo Art Gallery come May. From time to time she bribes the karaoke guy with flowers for two songs instead of one.

Steffanie Ling is a writer, curator and editor. She will have red wine and turtlenecks all year long. For LIT LIT LIT LIT she will be reading from work in process, tentatively titled “You’re a liar and a smoker” a book of twenty chapters for twenty cigarettes.

Zebulon Zang is a filmmaker and writer from Maillardville, British Columbia. He is also the founder of the Maillardville Cultural Appreciation Society, an exhibition space dedicated to the promotion of culture in peripheral zones.</description>
<enclosure url="http://litlitlitlit.xyz/podcasts/LITIPartI-ZebKara.mp3" length="68854786" type="audio/mpeg"/>
<category>Podcasts</category>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 11:30:00 -0500</pubDate>

<itunes:author>Emma Metcalfe Hurst</itunes:author>

<itunes:explicit>No</itunes:explicit>
<itunes:subtitle>LIT LIT LIT LIT Avenue 165 East Hastings St. Vancouver BC - Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen, Alex Bovril, and Steffanie Ling. April 18th 2015 8:00pm </itunes:subtitle>
<itunes:summary> LIT LIT LIT LIT Avenue 165 East Hastings St. Vancouver BC - Zebulon Zang, Kara Hansen, Alex Bovril, and Steffanie Ling. April 18th 2015 8:00pm </itunes:summary>
<itunes:duration>00:57:23</itunes:duration>
<itunes:keywords>Literature, Arts, Experimental, Performativity, Writing, GetLit, Reading, LITLITLITLIT</itunes:keywords>
</item>


</channel>
</rss>